Artificial and Ephemera 060
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Downtown DC - Downtown DC, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Downtown Progress - Downtown Progress, ca. 1960 (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Dupont Circle Citizens' Association - Dupont Circle Citizens' Association, 1940-1982 (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Dupont Circle Conservancy - Dupont Circle Conservancy, 1983-1984 (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - East Washington Citizens' Association - East Washington Citizens' Association, 1890-11-29 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - East Washington Heights Citizens Association - East Washington Heights Citizens Association, 1936 (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Eastpines Citizen's Association - Eastpines Citizen's Association, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Excelsior Literary Club - Excelsior Literary Club, 1920-1963 (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Fairlawn Citizens Association - Fairlawn Citizens Association, ca. 1984 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Bar Association - Federal Bar Association, 1936-1944 (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Federal Club, The, 1938-1956 (Box 42, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Bulletin, 1933-1938 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Bulletin, 1939-1945 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Bulletin, 1946-1949 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Bulletin, 1948-1953 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Member List, 1921-1925 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Member List, 1926-1929 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Member List, 1932-1937 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Member List, 1942-1946 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Club, The - Roster, 1948-1955 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federal Dramatic Clubs of Washington, The - Federal Dramatic Clubs of Washington, The, 1919-12-23 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federation of Citizens Association - Federation of Citizens Association, 1926-1948 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federation of Citizens Association - Directories, 1943-1958 (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federation of Citizens Association - Reports, 1936-1943 (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Federation of Women's Club - Federation of Women's Club, 1948-1950 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Forest Hills Citizens' Association - Forest Hills Citizens' Association, 1930-1944 (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Fort Dupont Citizens Association - Fort Dupont Citizens Association, 1949 (Box 44, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Fort Stanton Civic Association - Fort Stanton Civic Association, 1949-1985 (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Fotocraft Camera Club - Fotocraft Camera Club, 1940-1997 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Foxhall Citizens Association - Foxhall Citizens Association, 1942 (Box 44, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Friends of Ruth - Friends of Ruth, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Friendship Citizens' Association - Friendship Citizens' Association, 1941-1948 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Gentlemen's Charitable Association - Gentlemen's Charitable Association, 1858-09-30 (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - George Washington Memorial Association - George Washington Memorial Association, 1899-06 (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Glover Park Citizens Association - Glover Park Citizens Association, 1970-1988 (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Goethe-Institut Washington - Goethe-Institut Washington, 1996-06-14 (Box 44, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Greater Washington Committee for Unitarian Advance - Greater Washington Committee for Unitarian Advance, 1957-03-01 (Box 44, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Hadassah, Washington Chapter - Hadassah, Washington Chapter (Box 44, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Hamburgh Citizens' Association - Hamburgh Citizens' Association, 1964-10 (Box 44, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Hampshire Heights Citizen's Association - Hampshire Heights Citizen's Association, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Hebrew Benevolent Associations - Hebrew Benevolent Associations, 1876-01-20 (Box 44, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Historical Society of Washington, DC - Historical Society of Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 44, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Home Club, The - Home Club, The, 1913-11-12 (Box 44, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Home Interest Club - Home Interest Club, 1911 (Box 44, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - House of Mercy - House of Mercy, 1948-1956 (Box 44, Folder 24)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Institute for Government Research - Institute for Government Research, 1920-1922 (Box 44, Folder 25)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Instructive Visiting Nurse Society of Washington - Instructive Visiting Nurse Society of Washington, 1940 (Box 44, Folder 26)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Interior Department Recreation Association - Interior Department Recreation Association, 1939 (Box 44, Folder 27)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - John Carroll Society, The - John Carroll Society, The, 1997 (Box 44, Folder 28)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Kalorama Citizens' Association - Kalorama Citizens' Association, 1931-1966 (Box 44, Folder 29)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - League of Washington Theatres - League of Washington Theatres, 2004-2005 (Box 44, Folder 30)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - League of Women Voters - League of Women Voters, 1936-1950 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Lincoln Park Citizens' Association - Lincoln Park Citizens' Association, 1934-1942 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Little Sisters of the Poor - Little Sisters of the Poor (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - MacArthur Boulevard Citizens' Association - MacArthur Boulevard Citizens' Association, 1949 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday Commission - Martin Luther King, Jr. Federal Holiday Commission, 1986 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Masonic, 1908-1961 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Anacostia Lodge, 1906 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Anchor Masonic Club, 1935-10-24 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Grand Lodge of the District of Columbia, 1911-1961 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Lafayette Lodge, 1913 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Masonic Mutual Relief Association, 1908-1921 (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Masonic Temple Association, 1910 (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Potomac Lodge, 1953 (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Scottish Rite Temple, 1912-1943 (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Theodore Roosevelt Lodge, 1939-1942 (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Masonic - Washington Council, 1954-04-19 (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Montgomery Sycamore Island Club - Montgomery Sycamore Island Club, 1982 (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade - Metropolitan Washington Board of Trade, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Mignon Club - Mignon Club, 1883-01-17 (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People, 1978 (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - National Association for the Relief of Destitute Colored Women and Children - National Association for the Relief of Destitute Colored Women and Children, 1864-1915 (Box 45, Folder 21)
  all photocopies
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - National Catholic Welfare Conference - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1928-06 (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - National Conference of State Societies - National Conference of State Societies, 1968 (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - National Press Club - National Press Club, 1934-05-10 (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Neighborhood House - Neighborhood House (Box 45, Folder 25)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Neighbor's Inc. - Neighbor's Inc., 1974-1977 (Box 45, Folder 26)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Northeast Conference of Citizens' Associations - Northeast Conference of Citizens' Associations, 1942 (Box 45, Folder 27)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Northwest House, The - Northwest House, The, 1935-1938 (Box 45, Folder 28)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Northwest Suburban Citizens' Association - Northwest Suburban Citizens' Association, 1923-05-11 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Oldest Inhabitants' Association, 1880-1942 (Box 45, Folder 30)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by A. G. Riddle (Box 45, Folder 31)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by E. R. Mckean, 1895-02-22 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by Horatio N. Easby, 1876-01-05 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by John S. Lindsay, 1887 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by Peter G. Washington, 1867 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Oldest Inhabitants' Association - Address by Theodore W. Noyes, 1909-12-07 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Palisades Citizens Association - Palisades Citizens Association, 1950-1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Parkview Women's Club - Parkview Women's Club, 1931-1941 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Paul Robeson Friendship Society - Paul Robeson Friendship Society, 1978-07-20 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Petworth Citizens' Association - Petworth Citizens' Association, 1915-1937 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Petworth Girl Scout Troop Number 6 - Petworth Girl Scout Troop Number 6, 1915-1918 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Petworth Women's Club, The - Petworth Women's Club, The, 1945 (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Peoples Involvement Corporation, The - Peoples Involvement Corporation, The, 1970-04 (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Piney Branch Citizens Association - Piney Branch Citizens Association, 1910-05 (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Postal Photographic Club - Postal Photographic Club, 1888-1911 (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Pride, Inc. - Pride, Inc., 1969 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  "rat patrol"
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Progressive Citizens Association of Georgetown, The - Progressive Citizens Association of Georgetown, The, 1955 (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Queer Wheelmen - Queer Wheelmen, 1896-07-04 (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Rhode Island Avenue Citizens Association - Rhode Island Avenue Citizens Association, 1933-1957 (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - River Terrace Community Organization - River Terrace Community Organization, 1957-1962 (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Saint Andrew's Society - Saint Andrew's Society, 1963-1964 (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Sales Executives' Club of Washington - Sales Executives' Club of Washington (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Sanitary League, The - Sanitary League, The, 1893 (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Self-Determination for DC Coalition - Self-Determination for DC Coalition, 1985 (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Seymour Club - Seymour Club, 1921-1939 (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Shield of Honor, The: Tris Lodge - Shield of Honor, The: Tris Lodge, ca. 1900 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Shrine Committee, Almas Temple - Shrine Committee, Almas Temple, 1923 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Sixteenth Street Heights Club - Sixteenth Street Heights Club, 1931-1936 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Social Hygiene Society - Social Hygiene Society, 1936-1943 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Society of Washington Fakirs - Society of Washington Fakirs, 1899-1912 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Southeast Council of Citizens Associations - Southest Council of Citizens Associations, 1941 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Southeast Dramatics Association, The - Southeast Dramatics Association, The, 1948-1949 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Southeast Washington Citizens' Association - Southeast Washington Citizens' Association, 1944-1951 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Special Libraries Association - Special Libraries Association, 1990-11-14 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Takoma Park Citizens Association - Takoma Park Citizens Association, 1928-1939 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Ten Miles Square Club - Ten Miles Square Club (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Thespian Study Club, City of Washington, The - Thespian Study Club, City of Washington, The, 1951-03 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Torch Club, The - Torch Club, The, 1928-1938 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Torch Club, The - Yearbooks, 1930-1939 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Torch Club, The - Yearbooks, 1940-1949 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Torch Club, The - Yearbooks, 1950-1953 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Town Hall, The - Town Hall, The, 1936-1937 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Traffic Club of Washington, DC, The - Traffic Club of Washington, DC, The, 1938-1944 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Traffic Club of Washington, DC, The - Traffic Club of Washington, DC, The, 1946-1954 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Tuesday Women's Club, The - Tuesday Women's Club, The, 1938-1956 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Union Soldiers Alliance - Union Soldiers Alliance, 1912-1918 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - University Club of Washington - University Club of Washington, 1904-1917 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Visiting Nurse Society - Visiting Nurse Society, ca. 1950 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Animal Rescue League - Washington Animal Rescue League, 1944-1945 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Area Convention and Visitors Bureau - News Releases, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Washington Board of Trade, 1909-1959 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - News Releases, 1945 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Newsletters, 1937-1965 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - "Destination Washington, DC", 1951 (Box 48, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - Handbook, 1895 (Box 48, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - "People Jobs Homes", 1946 (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - "Population and Business Propects", 1944 (Box 48, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - "Sixty Years", 1949 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Publications - "Working for Washington" (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Reports, 1894-1953 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Statements and Speeches, 1938-1958 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Board of Trade - Surveies, 1927-1929 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Casino Association - Washington Casino Association, 1883-12-5 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Chamber of Commerce - Washington Chamber of Commerce, 1909-1926 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Drama Society - Washington Drama Society, 1963 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Garden Club - Washington Garden Club, 1933-1946 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Highlands Citizens Association - Washington Highlands Citizens Association, 1947 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Housing Association - Washington Housing Association, 1948-1949 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Home Rule Committee - Washington Home Rule Committee, 1948-1974 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington International Assembly, The - Washington International Assembly, The (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Jazz Club - Washington Jazz Club, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington League for the Hard of Hearing, The - Washington League for the Hard of Hearing, The, 1930-1937 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Medical and Surgical Society - Washington Medical and Surgical Society, 1939 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Photographic Society - Washington Photographic Society, 1937 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Road Club - Washington Road Club, 1896-05-30 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Sculptors Group - Washington Sculptors Group, 1957 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Society of Cinematographers, The - Washington Society of Cinematographers, The, 1954-03-01 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Story League, The - Washington Story League, The, 1939-1954 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Story League, The - Washington Story League, The, 1968-1979 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Study - Washington Study, 1927 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Taxpayers Association - Washington Taxpayers Association, 1938-03-24 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Urban League - Washington Urban League, 1943-1955 (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Wanderlusters, The - Washington Wanderlusters, The, 1922 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Water Color Club - Washington Water Color Club, 1948 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Washington Youth Council - Washington Youth Council, 1940 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - West End Citizens Association - West End Citizens Association (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Wisteria Pleasure Club - Wisteria Pleasure Club, 1882 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Wives of Executives of the Federal Independent Agencies - Wives of Executives of the Federal Independent Agencies, 1956-03-22 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Christian Temperance Union - Women's Christian Temperance Union, 1880-1928 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's National Democratic Club - Women's National Democratic Club, 1985 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's National Press Association - Women's National Press Association, 1903 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Army and Navy League - Women's Army and Navy League, 1916 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Bar Association - Women's Bar Association, 1936-1942 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Christian Association - Women's Christian Association, 1906 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Clinic Auxiliary, The - Women's Clinic Auxiliary, The, 1913-1914 (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's Committee of the USO Council - Women's Committee of the USO Council, 1944-1945 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Women's National Press Club - Women's National Press Club, 1927 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Woodburn Citizens' Association - Woodburn Citizens' Association, 1894-1909 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1866-1940 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1908-1911 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA), 1854-1872 (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Societies, Clubs and Organizations - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) - Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA), 1932 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Sports - Baseball - Baseball (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Sports - Baseball - Scorecards, 1893-1907 (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Sports - Baseball - Sporting News, 1899 (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Sports - Baseball - Twangers, 1988 (Box 50, Folder 24)
- Sports - Baseball - Washington Senators (Box 50, Folder 25)
- Sports - Football - Washington Redskins (Box 50, Folder 26)
- Sports - Horse Racing - Horse Racing, 1940-06-22 (Box 50, Folder 27)
- Sports - President's Cup Regatta - President's Cup Regatta, 1956 (Box 50, Folder 28)
- Sports - Roller Skating - Roller Skating (Box 50, Folder 29)